export default class Question4 {
  public static question: Question4[] = [
    {
      question: 'What is a common red flag indicating a potential phising website',
      answers: [
        'A The website adress starts with "https://"',
        'B The website has a professional and polished appearance',
        'C The URL contains misspelled',
        'D The website claims to offer exclusive deals and discounts',
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'C The URL contains misspelled',
      explanation: 'The URL contains misspelled words or random charachters',
    },
    {
      question: 'What is the purpose of clearing browser cookies and cache regularly?',
      answers: [
        'A To speed up internet browsing',
        'B To enhance website functionality',
        'C To remove stored personal information and improve privacy',
        'D To increase the risk of online tracking'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'C To remove stored personal information and improve privacy',
      explanation: 'To remove stored personal information and improve privacy?',
    },
    {
      question: 'What is the primary purpose of a firewall in computer security?',
      answers: [
        'A To detect and remove viruses',
        'B To prevent unauthorized acces to a network',
        'C To encrypt sensitive data',
        'D To optimize network performance'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'B To prevent unauthorized acces to a network',
      explanation: 'To prevent unauthorized access to a network',
    },
    {
      question: 'How does biometric authentication enhance security?',
      answers: [
        'A By using physical keys for access',
        'B By relying on something you know, like a password',
        'C By utilizing unique physical or behavioral traits for identification',
        'D By requiring multiple forms of identification'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'C By utilizing unique physical or behavioral traits for identification',
      explanation: 'By utilizing unique physical or behavioral traits for identification',
    },
    {
      question: 'What is the potential risk of oversharing personal information on social media platforms?',
      answers: [
        'A Increased online popularity',
        'B Enhanced personal security',
        'C Privacy invasion and targeted attacks',
        'D Improved social connections'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'C Privacy invasion and targeted attacks',
      explanation: 'Privacy invasion and targeted attacks',
    },
    {
      question: 'What does VPN stand for in the context of online privacy?',
      answers: [
        'A Virtual Private Network',
        'B Very Private Navigation',
        'C Virus Protection Network',
        'D Visual Privacy Node'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'A Virtual Private Network',
      explanation: 'Virtual Private Network',
    },
    {
      question: 'What is the potential risk of using public Wi-Fi networks?',
      answers: [
        'A Faster internet speed',
        'B Increased device performance',
        'C Unauthorized access to personal information',
        'D Improved network security'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'C Unauthorized access to personal information',
      explanation: 'Unauthorized access to personal information',
    },
    {
      question: 'What does HTTPS stand for in the context of web browsing?',
      answers: [
        'A HyperText Transfer Protocol Secure',
        'B High-Efficiency Text Processing System',
        'C Home Technology and Entertainment Platform',
        'D Hyperlink Transmission System'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'A HyperText Transfer Protocol Secure',
      explanation: 'HyperText Transfer Protocol Secure',
    },
    {
      question: 'Why is it important to use different passwords for various online accounts?',
      answers: [
        'A It is not necessary; the same password can be used for convenience',
        'B To avoid the hassle of remembering multiple passwords',
        'C To minimize the risk of multiple accounts being compromised if one password is leaked',
        'D To make it easier for password recovery',
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'C To minimize the risk of multiple accounts being compromised if one password is leaked',
      explanation: 'To minimize the risk of multiple accounts being compromised if one password is leaked',
    },
    {
      question: ' Which of the following is an example of a strong password policy?',
      answers: [
        'A Allowing users to use the same password for multiple accounts',
        'B Requiring passwords to be at least 8 characters long',
        'C Discouraging the use of special characters in passwords',
        'D Implementing no restrictions on password complexity'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'B Requiring passwords to be at least 8 characters long',
      explanation: 'Requiring passwords to be at least 8 characters long',
    },
    {
      question: 'How can a passphrase be more secure than a single-word password?',
      answers: [
        'A Passphrases are always less secure',
        'B Passphrases are easier to crack',
        'C Passphrases are longer and include spaces between words',
        'D Passphrases are less memorable'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'C Passphrases are longer and include spaces between words',
      explanation: 'Passphrases are longer and include spaces between words',
    },
    {
      question: 'What is the recommended frequency for changing passwords to enhance security?',
      answers: [
        'A Every month',
        'B Only when a security breach occurs',
        'C Every few years',
        'D Never, if the password is strong and unique'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'D Never, if the password is strong and unique',
      explanation: 'Never, if the password is strong and unique',
    },
    {
      question: 'Which of the following password management practices is insecure',
      answers: [
        'A Using a password manager to generate and store complex passwords',
        'B Writing down passwords on a sticky note and keeping it on the monitor',
        'C Changing passwords every few years',
        'D Sharing passwords with close family members'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'B Writing down passwords on a sticky note and keeping it on the monitor',
      explanation: 'Writing down passwords on a sticky note and keeping it on the monitor',
    },
    {
      question: 'Which of the following passwords is the most secure?',
      answers: [
        'A password123',
        'B P@ssw0rd',
        'C qwerty',
        'D 123456'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'B P@ssw0rd',
      explanation: 'P@ssw0rd',
    },
    {
      question: 'What is a recommended practice for creating strong passwords?',
      answers: [
        'A Using easily memorable phrases',
        'B Incorporating personal information like birthdates',
        'C Using a mix of uppercase and lowercase letters, numbers, and symbols',
        'D Keeping the same password across multiple accounts'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'C Using a mix of uppercase and lowercase letters, numbers, and symbols',
      explanation: 'Using a mix of uppercase and lowercase letters, numbers, and symbols',
    },
    {
      question: 'Why is it important to avoid using easily guessable passwords?',
      answers: [
        'A Because they are easier to remember',
        'B To make it more challenging for unauthorized access',
        'C They are less likely to be accepted by websites',
        'D To confuse the user'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'B To make it more challenging for unauthorized access',
      explanation: 'To make it more challenging for unauthorized access',
    },
    {
      question: 'What is the purpose of Two-Factor Authentication (2FA)?',
      answers: [
        'A Enhancing password security by requiring two different passwords',
        'B Providing a second layer of verification in addition to a password',
        'C Encrypting all data on a device',
        'D Allowing access without any authentication'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'B Providing a second layer of verification in addition to a password',
      explanation: 'Providing a second layer of verification in addition to a password',
    },
    {
      question: 'Which of the following is considered a strong password practice?',
      answers: [
        'A Using easily guessable words like "password123"',
        'B Using a combination of uppercase and lowercase letters',
        'C Sharing passwords with trusted friends',
        'D Keeping the same password for all accounts'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'B Using a combination of uppercase and lowercase letters',
      explanation: 'Using a combination of uppercase and lowercase letters',
    },
    {
      question: 'Which of the following passwords is the most secure?',
      answers: [
        'A patat123',
        'B HetIsPatat#@!2',
        'C friet',
        'D WZAWZDB'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'B HetIsPatat#@!2',
      explanation: 'HetIsPatat#@!2',
    },
    {
      question: 'Which of the following passwords is the most secure?',
      answers: [
        'A Fortnite123',
        'B Skulltrooper1',
        'C #@Roblox23:',
        'D FreeVBucks'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'C #@Roblox23:',
      explanation: '#@Roblox23:',
    },
    {
      question: 'How can you verify the legitimacy of an email sender?',
      answers: [
        'A Click on any links provided in the email',
        'B Check the sender email address for authenticity',
        'C Respond to the email with personal information',
        'D Forward the email to friends for confirmation',
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'B Check the sender email address for authenticity',
      explanation: 'Check the sender email address for authenticity',
    },
    {
      question: 'What is a common sign of a phishing email?',
      answers: [
        'A Personalized greetings using your name',
        'B Urgent requests for immediate action',
        'C Clear and professional formatting',
        'D Inclusion of legitimate contact information'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'B Urgent requests for immediate action',
      explanation: 'Urgent requests for immediate action',
    },
    {
      question: 'What should you do if you receive an unexpected email requesting sensitive information?',
      answers: [
        'A Provide the requested information to verify your identity',
        'B Ignore the email and mark it as spam',
        'C Share the email on social media for advice',
        'D Reply with a request for more information about the sender'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'B Ignore the email and mark it as spam',
      explanation: 'Ignore the email and mark it as spam',
    },
    {
      question: 'How can you verify the safety of a link before clicking on it?',
      answers: [
        'A Click on the link and check the website for legitimacy',
        'B Hover over the link to preview the destination URL',
        'C Share the link on social media for feedback',
        'D Trust links that promise exclusive deals and discounts'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'B Hover over the link to preview the destination URL',
      explanation: 'Hover over the link to preview the destination URL',
    },
    {
      question: 'What is the significance of "https://" in a website URL?',
      answers: [
        'A It indicates a highly discounted website',
        'B It signifies a secure and encrypted connection',
        'C It means the website has fast loading times',
        'D It suggests the website is exclusive and trustworthy'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'B It signifies a secure and encrypted connection',
      explanation: 'It signifies a secure and encrypted connection',
    },
    {
      question: 'What should you look for in the address bar to ensure a website is secure?',
      answers: [
        'A An absence of any symbols or icons',
        'B A green padlock icon and "https://" at the beginning of the URL',
        'C A red warning sign indicating excitement',
        'D A blue checkmark next to the website name'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'A green padlock icon and "https://" at the beginning of the URL',
      explanation: 'green padlock icon and "https://" at the beginning of the URL',
    },
    {
      question: 'Why is it important to verify the authenticity of a website before entering personal information?',
      answers: [
        'A To increase the websites popularity',
        'B To avoid encountering interesting content',
        'C To prevent unauthorized access and data theft',
        'D To test the effectiveness of your antivirus software'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'C To prevent unauthorized access and data theft',
      explanation: 'To prevent unauthorized access and data theft',
    },
    {
      question: 'Why is it important to review a websites privacy policy before providing personal information?',
      answers: [
        'A To check the websites popularity',
        'B To understand how the website will handle and protect your data',
        'C To speed up the websites loading times',
        'D To verify the websites encryption level'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'B To understand how the website will handle and protect your data',
      explanation: 'To understand how the website will handle and protect your data',
    },
    {
      question: 'What should you do if you receive an email with a link claiming to be from a familiar organization?',
      answers: [
        'A Click on the link to confirm its authenticity',
        'B Forward the email to all your contacts for verification',
        'C Contact the organization directly using official contact information',
        'D Ignore the email without further investigation'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'C Contact the organization directly using official contact information',
      explanation: 'Contact the organization directly using official contact information',
    },
    {
      question: 'When creating an Instagram account, what type of account is the safest one?',
      answers: [
        'A Private account',
        'B Public account',
        'C Business account',
        'D Meme account'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'A Private account',
      explanation: 'Private account',
    },
    {
      question: 'If you need to connect to Wi-Fi outside of your house, where is the safest place to do it?',
      answers: [
        'A You connect to the Wi-Fi of a popular store',
        'B You connect to any free Wi-Fi network',
        'C You connect to Wi-Fi using a VPN (Virtual Private Network)',
        'D You connect to the Wi-Fi of restaurant'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'C You connect to Wi-Fi using a VPN (Virtual Private Network)',
      explanation: 'You connect to Wi-Fi using a VPN (Virtual Private Network)',
    },
    {
      question: 'Your online friend asks you to send the photo of your identity card. What do you do?',
      answers: [
        'A You send a picture of your identity card',
        'B You do not send your identity card',
        'C You send them a photograph of you',
        'D You send a picture of your grandma'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'B You do not send your identity card',
      explanation: 'You do not send your identity card',
    },
    {
      question: 'What does it mean to have a lock sign before a link in your browser?',
      answers: [
        'A This site is safe to enter personal details',
        'B This site is unsafe to enter personal details',
        'C This site is not kids-friendly',
        'D This site is private'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'A This site is safe to enter personal details',
      explanation: 'This site is safe to enter personal details',
    },
    {
      question: 'You get an email asking for your house address in order to deliver some prize to you. What do you do?',
      answers: [
        'A You give them the address, because there is a prize to get',
        'B You give them the address of your friend to make them a surprise',
        'C You verify if the email is reliable and decide upon it with your',
        'D You answer the email'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'C You verify if the email is reliable and decide upon it with your',
      explanation: 'You verify if the email is reliable and decide upon it with your',
    },
    {
      question: 'You enter a gaming website and you are asked to download extensions to be able to play. What do you do?',
      answers: [
        'A You first download it in the computer of your parents',
        'B You first check if the extensions are safe',
        'C You first download it, because you must play this game',
        'D You first check if the extentions are awesome'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'B You first check if the extensions are safe',
      explanation: 'You first check if the extensions are safe',
    }
  ];

  public static dumpQuestions: Question4[] = [];
}
